freeziki.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy - Howwe

When you use our website, you trust us with some of your information. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

## How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

      • To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
      • To improve our website in order to better serve you.  
      • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
      • To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

## How do we protect visitor information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

**We do not use an SSL certificate**  
      • **We do not need an SSL because:** We only provide articles and information and do not at any point transmit or publish our users sensitive private data (e.g. email address, ip address) over the internet.

## Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**  
      • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
      • Keep track of advertisements.  
      • Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

### **If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

**You will not be able to :**

  * **Logging in -** You'll not be able to log in to our website
  * **Commenting -** If you're not logged in, you'll not be able to comment to any of our posts
  * **Post interaction -** You won't be able to like, dislike or vote on the posts on our website

### **How to control and delete cookies**

If you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by our website, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your browser settings. The “Help” function within your browser should tell you how to activate the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies.

Alternatively you may wish to visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which contains comprehensive information about how to restrict or block cookies on a wide variety of browsers. You will also find information about how to delete cookies from your machine as well as more general information about cookies.

### **Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### **Google Analytics**

We also use Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it.

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site.

Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page.

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page.

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

#### **Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on**

To provide website visitors the ability to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics, Google developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, dc.js). [**Opt-out here >>**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

### **Log Files**

Our systems automatically gather some anonymous information about visitors, including IP addresses, browser type, language, and the times and dates of webpage visits.  The data collected does not include personally identifiable information and is used, as described above, for statistical analysis, to understand user behaviour, and to administer the site.

### **Social Media**

If you share our content through social media, for example by liking us on Facebook, following or tweeting about us on Twitter, or giving us a '+1' via Google Plus, those social networks will record that you have done so and may set a cookie for this purpose.

In some cases, where a page on our website includes content from a social network, such as a Twitter feed, or Facebook comments box, those services may set a cookie even where you do not click a button.  As is the case for all cookies, we cannot access those set by social networks, just as those social networks cannot access cookies we set ourselves.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

**Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:**  
      • On our Privacy Policy Page  
**Users are able to change their personal information:**  
      • By logging in to their account

## How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

## Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking

## COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

## Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**  
**We will notify the users via email**  
      • Within 1 business day  
**We will notify the users via in site notification**  
      • Within 1 business day

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

## CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**  
      • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**  
      • NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses  
      • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way  
      • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters  
      • Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
      • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly  
      • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**  
      • Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Howwe Ltd  
Kabalagala - Muyenga Road  
Kampala, 256 Uganda  
howwebiz@gmail.com

_**This policy was last updated 2015-12-01**_
